From this version, we have optimized the functions related to the
basic settings.
We can add correct sewing information to the version, and then switch to the print and
release mode, click on the fabric in the object window, and set the width and width in the
property editor.
Similarly, you can also modify the width and width in the material settings.
You can also manually set the length of the sale price, so that the version can be
calculated in the length of the setting.
You can also modify the unit here, and then we can further set the direction of the
material as double, and you can also change the length of the material according to the
needed length of the fabric.
We can also set the number of clothing that you need to choose one or four to
calculate the material.
We can also set the space between the fabric and the fabric to be in the place.
Then we can set the number of clothes that need to be arms here.
When 3D clothing is out, we can calculate the unit number of the machine horse and
estimate the material cost in a single row way.
In the current scene, we can directly enter the current size of the clothing number at the
Then we enter three keys here.
After completing the layout setting, we can click the plate layout button to start the layout.
When the progress bar is close to 100%, and the layout picture is no longer changing, you can click here to stop the layout to stop the current layout calculation.
After the layout is completed, we can see that the name of the fabric is displayed at the top of the layout area, the direction of the sand line, and the number of plates placed in the current layout area.
The name of the file is displayed on the left side, with the length and volume of the material, and the width and volume of the fabric are displayed on the right side, as well as the number of keys.
We can also find these information in the property editor.
In the previous version, we need to select different fabrics to arrange them separately.
But from this version, when we switch to different fabrics, we can see that other fabrics have also been arranged.
When you need to rearrange, you can reset the arrangement settings,
and then click to remove the extra fabric sheets to delete the excess sheets, and then do the fabric operation.
Click to reset the default arrangement.
You can closely arrange the current scattered sheets to the fabric area and display them at the top position.
When the 3D riding suit is finished, we can also calculate the number of mixed-race fabrics in the print and release mode.
In the property editor of the single machine, select the riding button on the right side of the number of clothes.
Enter the number of each size keys that need to be lined in the spring.
We can enter the total number of clothes on the top.
Click to enter the value and quickly modify all the number of size keys.
If we need to set the number of each size key according to the scale,
you can also modify the S and XL numbers here as one key.
We can also select to divide the clothes according to the size of each size.
This is also the new function we added this time.
Similar, next we will choose the color of the need to be lined.
If you only need to line the current color, then you can choose the current color.
You can also choose the color according to your needs.
If you only need to line the current color, then you can choose the color according to your needs.
Click to select the color button on the right side of the color, and click to select the color information in the spring.
The color that is selected will be lined together when lining.
Now you can see that the lining has been completed.
When we open the display to put the code in random colors, you can see clearly.
The version is divided into different size versions according to the size of the horse.
Close the display to put the code in random colors.
When we switch the horse, the position of the current horse version will be highlighted.
Switch the flag color, you can see that the flag color that is selected has been lined together.
If you want to show the pattern, you can click on the quick photo.
After setting the size of the pattern according to the needs and the information that needs to be displayed,
Click to save and you can save the file to this machine.
I hope this video can help you better understand the function update content and application scenarios of this print and print.
Make your print and print operation more flexible and smooth.
Hurry up and open the software and try it.